Are teenage dreams so hard to beat?
Good Vibrations is a music, drama film directed by Lisa Barros D'Sa.
The story of music legend Terri Hooley, a key
figure in Belfast's punk rock scene.
Hooley founded the Good Vibrations store from which a record label sprung,
representing bands such as The Undertones, Rudi and The Outcasts.
Terri Hooley, played by Richard Dormer.
Ruth, played by Jodie Whittaker.
George Hooley, played by Karl Johnson.
Dave Hyndman, played by Michael Colgan.
Davy, played by Liam Cunningham.
Pat, played by Dylan Moran.
Good Vibrations is a 2013 comedy-drama film written by Colin Carberry and Glenn
Patterson and directed by Lisa Barros D'Sa and Glenn Leyburn.
It stars Richard Dormer, Jodie Whittaker, Adrian Dunbar,
Liam Cunningham, Karl Johnson and Dylan Moran.
It is based on the life of Terri Hooley, a record-store owner
instrumental in developing Belfast's punk rock scene.
The film was produced by Chris Martin, with Andrew
Eaton, Bruno Charlesworth and David Holmes.
Holmes also co-wrote the soundtrack score.
The tone is emotional.